<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects | Scott I. Donaldson, PhD</title>
    <link>www.scottdonaldsonphd.com/project/</link>
      <atom:link href="www.scottdonaldsonphd.com/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Projects</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Scott Donaldson, 2023</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/www.scottdonaldsonphd.com/images/icon_hua2ec155b4296a9c9791d015323e16eb5_11927_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>www.scottdonaldsonphd.com/project/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>IPPA Work and Organizations</title>
      <link>www.scottdonaldsonphd.com/project/external-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>www.scottdonaldsonphd.com/project/external-project/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bridging the Gap between Academia and Practice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of the Tobacco-Use Prevention Education Program</title>
      <link>www.scottdonaldsonphd.com/project/internal-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>www.scottdonaldsonphd.com/project/internal-project/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a Post-Doctoral Scholar at the University of California, San Diego School of Medicine, I advanced my transdisciplinary research interests in evaluation, statistics, and measurement by designing a grant electronic monitoring and evaluation software system for a statewide behavioral health intervention in California. Under the supervision of world-renowned Chinese scientist Shu-Hong Zhu, I conducted a comprehensive theory-driven evaluation of an evidence-based education program with $60 million in allocated funds from the California Department of Education. Our real-time monitoring, evaluation, and technical assistance approach integrated continuous quality improvement to help design, measure, and evaluate the impact of a multi-tiered socioecological prevention program.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tobacco Industry Monitoring Evaluation</title>
      <link>www.scottdonaldsonphd.com/project/time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>www.scottdonaldsonphd.com/project/time/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The main goal of the project is to inform comprehensive tobacco control policy efforts by monitoring core tobacco industry practices related to electronic cigarettes and other new and emerging non-combustible nicotine products, and little cigars and cigarillos in three core tobacco industry practices: advertising and marketing on social media platforms, direct marketing, and underage online sales.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
